{
    "subject": "resource/Michael_Connelly",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Ross_Macdonald",
    "human_readable": "Michael Connelly was influenced by Ross Macdonald.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9106556177139282,
            "question": "Who influenced Michael Connelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9044397473335266,
            "question": "How did Ross Macdonald's influence shape Michael Connelly's writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8711338043212891,
            "question": "Name a notable author who influenced Michael Connelly."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7754831910133362,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Michael Connelly and Ross Macdonald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7173411846160889,
            "question": "Are there any other authors who were influenced by Ross Macdonald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6657581925392151,
            "question": "What common themes might be found in the works of both Michael Connelly and Ross Macdonald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.429638534784317,
            "question": "Was Ross Macdonald a writer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39945393800735474,
            "question": "Who are some famous authors that Ross Macdonald might have inspired?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2851203978061676,
            "question": "Can you name any works by Ross Macdonald?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2347971796989441,
            "question": "What genre of writing is Michael Connelly known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michael Connelly was influenced by Ross Macdonald.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5875_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any works by Ross Macdonald?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5875_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous authors that Ross Macdonald might have inspired?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5875_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Ross Macdonald a writer?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5875_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_143.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5875_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Michael Connelly lists Joseph Wambaugh as another of his main influences, and Ross Macdonald as one of his main influences. This implies that he was influenced by both authors, including specifically Ross Macdonald."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Michael Connelly lists Ross Macdonald as one of his main influences, which supports the statement that Michael Connelly was influenced by Ross Macdonald."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}